theme: Назовите страну по её столице
level: 1
questions:
  - question: "Пекин"
    answers: ["Китай"]
  - question: "Вашингтон"
    answers: [ "США" ]
  - question: "Бразилиа"
    answers: [ "Бразилия" ]
  - question: "Анкара"
    answers: [ "Турция" ]
  - question: "Лондон"
    answers: [ "Великобритания" ]
  - question: "Каир"
    answers: [ "Египет" ]
  - question: "Токио"
    answers: [ "Япония" ]
  - question: "Мадрид"
    answers: [ "Испания" ]
  - question: "Амстердам"
    answers: [ "Нидерланды", "Голандия" ]
  - question: "Оттава"
    answers: [ "Канада" ]
  - question: "Сеул"
    answers: [ "Южная Корея" ]
  - question: "Стокголм"
    answers: [ "Швеция" ]
  - question: "Эр-Рияд"
    answers: [ "Саудовская Аравия" ]
  - question: "Дублин"
    answers: [ "Ирландия" ]
  - question: "Прага"
    answers: [ "Чехия" ]
  - question: "Алжир"
    answers: [ "Алжир" ]
  - question: "Вена"
    answers: [ "Австрия" ]
  - question: "Сингапур"
    answers: [ "Сингапур" ]
  - question: "Осло"
    answers: [ "Норвегия" ]
  - question: "Буэнос-Айрес"
    answers: [ "Аргентина" ]
  - question: "Брюссель"
    answers: [ "Бельгия" ]
  - question: "Загреб"
    answers: [ "Хорватия" ]
  - question: "Хельсинки"
    answers: [ "Финляндия" ]
  - question: "Копенгаген"
    answers: [ "Дания" ]
  - question: "Бангкок"
    answers: [ "Тайланд" ]
  - question: "Сантьяго"
    answers: [ "Чили" ]
  - question: "Любляна"
    answers: [ "Словения" ]
  - question: "Джакарта"
    answers: [ "Индонезия" ]
  - question: "Кабул"
    answers: [ "Афганистан" ]
  - question: "София"
    answers: [ "Болгария" ]

